Alright now we are going to show you how to read and write on some sheet music in the key of E flat.
So we will start with this nice piece of blank paper.
First you have your two basic clefts; your treble cleft and your basic cleft, so we will start here.
There's our treble cleft and E flat is this very first line.
Now each line and space is a note in the scale so the notes in between the scale, I notated was a flat or a sharp.
Here's your sharp symbol.
Now to make it easier on you, what they do is they put the treble cleft there and they put the three flats already in.
See that, E flat, E flat and A flat.
So now when we go through and play your scale, you will know that when you get to an A flat, B flat or E flat, it is going to be flat.
So there are your 7 notes; 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7.
So if you go back in the video and look in the pattern, you can see those 7 notes and now you can go see them on a piece of paper.